

# INFO

Surrey, BC 778-875-3767 smaynard4@my.bcit.ca

## **SKILLS**

#### **Web Development**

- · CSS, SCSS & HTML
- Javascript
- PHP
- · React
- Storybook
- Experienced in creating and altering code of Wordpress websitesp
- Collaborating or Github

## Design

- UX/UI design, testing and prototyping
- Logo/branding experience
- Photo Editing
- · Web Design
- Stanutalling
- · Design Research & strategy
- Versed in Wordpress
  Website building
- · Magazine Page Layout
- · Video Editing

# TOOLS

- Adobe Photoshop
- · Illustrator
- Photoshop
- Indesign
- Figma
- · Adobe Auditions
- · After Effects
- · Adobe Premiere
- Microsoft products (exce, Word, Power point)
- Sketch
- · Heat maps

# SHANNON MAYNARD

# Summary

I'm primarily focused on creating meaningful user experiences through UX/UI design which is complemented through my graphic design skills that add for better visual impacts. Recently, I've also been learning and practicing CRO skills, using tools such as heat maps, which I've found further complement both my UX/UI and graphic design skills. These skill combinations make my projects more user friendly, visually imapctful and while also having the practical benefit of active customer conversion

## **Education**

2019 - 2021

#### **BCIT Digital Design and Development diploma program**

After realising that a background in pure arts wasn't the right choice, I left Emily-Carr to pursue my true passion, digital design. At BCIT, I worked on many types of types of projects, where I learned how to develop, and creat dynamic solutions for cross-platform applications. Some of the major projects I worked on include website building through wordpress, as well as react applications, which I built with resuable components. Other Major projects include creating user friendly application designs and prototyping through tools such as figma. I also practiced creating style guides and user testing.

Through these projects. BCIT has taught me one of my best skills: communication. They constantly threw us together constantly into teams so we'd learn how properly collaborate with with a diverse group of team members. This skill has helped me in creating better and more consistent projects that take in other members inputs as well as my own.

2017

#### **Emily-Carr University Bachelor of Fine Arts Program**

During my time there, I deepened my art background by taking photography courses, art history, painting, and sound editing.

2016 Summer

# **Neighbourhood Arts Studio Portfolio Program**

Worked on different art mediums such as painting, drawing, and multi-media art for the purposes of creating a portfolio to enter Emily Carr University

2012-2014

## Panorama-Ridge Secondary School High school Diploma

Was part of a French Immersion program where I graduated with honours

## **Work History**

2019 - 2020

# **Junior Interior Painter:**

For the past year and a half, I've worked as a junior painter, painting home interiors. Learned how to talk to customers and work in a team environment

2013 - 2018

#### **Piano Tutor**

I started my own piano tutoring business through word of mouth and advertising with flyers. For five years, I taught many kids on foundational piano skills and helped them learn piano and improve for the Royal Conservitory Music examinations. I learned leadership skills and how to get students to follow my directions

2017 Summer

## **Customer Service at Farmers Market**

Worked in the deli, making food, and manning the cash register. Developed customer relationship skills